Guide to the Washington State University Publications: Athletics Football Programs 1906-
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Oct. 3, 1992 vs. Temple. Band / Future Cougar Day. (Box 11)
- Oct. 31, 1992 vs. Oregon. Dads' Day. (Box 11)
- Nov. 7, 1992 vs. Arizona State. (Box 11)
- Nov. 21, 1992 vs. Washington. (Box 11)
- Sept. 25, 1993 vs. USC. (Box 11)
- Oct. 9, 1993 vs. Arizona State. (Box 11)
- Oct. 16, 1993 vs. California. (Box 11)
- Dec. 31, 1994 vs. Baylor. Alamo Bowl. (Box 11)
- Sept. 2, 1995 vs. Pittsburgh. 2 different copies. (Box 12)
- Sept. 9, 1995 vs. Montana. 2 copies. (Box 12)
- Sept. 23, 1995 vs. UCLA. 2 copies. (Box 12)
- Oct. 7, 1995 vs. Oregon State. 3 copies. (Box 12)
- Oct. 28, 1995 vs. Arizona. 2 copies. (Box 12)
- Nov. 4, 1995 vs. California. (Box 12)
- Nov. 11, 1995 vs. Stanford. 2 copies. (Box 12)
- Nov. 18, 1995 vs. Washington. 2 different copies. (Box 12)
- Also in Box 12: Basketball --- Inland Empire, Tip-off Magazine, previews for WSU, Gonzaga, and EWU, 1995-1996 basketball teams, 1995-1996 Cougar Basketball vs Montana, Dec. 13, and vs Idaho, Dec. 16 (2 copies). (Box 12)
- Sept. 21, 1996 vs. Oregon. (Box 11)
- Sept. 28, 1996 vs. San Jose State. (Box 11)
- Oct. 19, 1996 vs. California. Homecoming (2 copies). (Box 11)
- Oct. 26, 1996 vs. USC. Dad's Day, Shrine Day. (Box 11)
- Nov. 23, 1996 vs. Washington. Apple Cup. (Box 11)
- Aug.30, 1997 vs. UCLA. (Box 11)
- Sept. 20, 1997 vs. Illinois. (Box 11)
- Sept. 27, 1997 vs. Boise State. Future Cougar Day, Band Day. (Box 11)
- Oct. 18, 1997 vs. California. Homecoming. (Box 11)
- Oct. 25, 1997 vs. Arizona. Land Grant Day. (Box 11)
- Nov. 15, 1997 vs. Stanford. (Box 11)
- Nov. 22, 1997 vs. Washington. Apple Cup. (Box 11)
- Sept. 5, 1998 vs. Illinois. Season Opener, Shrine Day. (Box 13)
- Sept. 19, 1998 vs. Idaho. Band Day, Future Cougar Day. (Box 13)
- Oct. 10, 1998 vs. Oregon. Homecoming, Land Grant Day. (Box 13)
- Oct. 17, 1998 vs. USC. WSU Foundation Day. (Box 13)
- Oct. 31, 1998 vs. Arizona State. Dad's Day. (Box 13)
- Sept. 4, 1999 vs. Utah. (Box 13)
- Sept. 18, 1999 vs. Idaho. (Box 13)
- Sept. 2, 2000 vs. Stanford. (Box 13)
- Sept. 23, 2000 vs. Idaho. (Box 13)
- Aug. 31, 2001 vs. Idaho. (Box 13)
- Sept. 15, 2001 vs. Colorado. (Box 13)
- Oct. 6, 2001 vs. Oregon State. (Box 13)
- Aug. 31, 2002 vs. Nevada. (Box 13)
- Sept. 7, 2002 vs. Idaho. (Box 13)
- Sept. 21, 2002 vs. Montana State. (Box 13)
- Oct. 5, 2002 vs. USC. (Box 13)
- Oct. 12, 2002 vs. Stanford. (Box 13)
- Nov. 2, 2002 vs. Arizona State. (Box 13)
- Nov. 9, 2002 vs. Oregon. (Box 13)
- Nov. 23, 2002 vs. Washington. (Box 13)
- Jan. 1, 2003 vs. Oklahoma. Rose Bowl (2 different copies). (Box 13)
- Sept. 6, 2003 vs. Notre Dame. (Box 14)
- Dec. 30, 2003 vs. Texas. Holiday Bowl. (Box 14)
- 1978-2002 Miracles & Memories: 25 Years of Holiday Bowl Magic. (Box 14)
- Facts & Figures (Holiday Bowl). (Box 14)
- 2003 Cougar Football (2003 Season Review, and 2003 Holiday Bowl Preview). (Box 14)
- Sept. 11, 2004 vs. Colorado. (Box 14)
- Sept. 18, 2004 vs. Idaho. (Box 14)
- Oct. 9, 2004 vs. Oregon. (Box 14)
- Oct. 16, 2004 vs. Stanford. (Box 14)
- Oct. 30, 2004 vs. USC. (Box 14)
- Nov. 20, 2004 vs. Washington. (Box 14)
- Sept. 1, 2005 vs. Idaho. (Box 14)
- Sept. 17, 2005 vs. Grambling. (Box 14)
- Oct. 8, 2005 vs. Stanford. (Box 14)
- Oct. 15, 2005 vs. UCLA. (Box 14)
- Oct. 22, 2005 vs. California. (Box 14)
- Nov. 5, 2005 vs. Arizona State. (Box 14)
- Nov. 12, 2005 vs. Oregon. (Box 14)
- Sept. 9, 2006 vs. Idaho. (Box 15)
- Sept. 30, 2006 vs. USC. (Box 15)
- Oct. 14, 2006 vs. California. (Box 15)
- Oct. 21, 2006 vs. Oregon. (Box 15)
- Nov. 4, 2006 vs. Arizona. (Box 15)
- Nov. 18, 2006 vs. Washington. (Box 15)
- Sept. 8, 2007 vs. San Diego State. (Box 15)
- Sept. 15, 2007 vs. Idaho. (Box 15)
- Oct. 27, 2007 vs. UCLA. (Box 15)
- Nov. 10, 2007 vs. Stanford. (Box 15)
- Nov. 17, 2007 vs. Oregon State. (Box 15)
- Aug. 30, 2008 vs. Oklahoma State. (Box 15)
- Sept. 6, 2008 vs. California. (Box 15)
- Sept. 27, 2008 vs. Oregon. (Box 15)
- Oct. 18, 2008 vs. USC. (Box 15)
- Nov. 8, 2008 vs. Arizona. (Box 15)
- Nov. 22, 2008 vs. Washington. (Box 15)
- Sept. 5, 2009 vs. Stanford. (Box 15)
- Sept. 12, 2009 vs. Hawaii. (Box 15)
- Sept. 19, 2009 vs. Southern Methodist. (Box 15)
- Oct. 10, 2009 vs. Arizona State. (Box 15)
- Nov. 14, 2009 vs. UCLA. (Box 15)
- Nov. 21, 2009 vs. Oregon State. (Box 15)
- Sept. 11, 2010 vs. Montana State. (Box 16)
- Oct. 9, 2010 vs. Oregon. (Box 16)
- Oct. 16, 2010 vs. Arizona. (Box 16)
- Nov. 6, 2010 vs. California. (Box 16)
- Dec. 4, 2010 vs. Washington. (Box 16)
- No 2011-2015 programs. (Box 16)
- Sept. 3, 2016 vs. Eastern Washington. (Box 16)
- Sept. 10, 2016 at Boise State. (Box 16)
- Sept. 17, 2016 vs. Idaho. (Box 16)
- Oct. 1, 2016 vs. Oregon. (Box 16)
- Oct. 15, 2016 vs. UCLA. (Box 16)
- Oct. 22, 2016 at Arizona State. (Box 16)
- Nov. 5, 2016 vs. Arizona. (Box 16)
- Nov. 12, 2016 vs. California. (Box 16)
- Nov. 25, 2016 vs. Washington. (Box 16)